(Leonard:)Oh, God.
(Leonard:)Sheldon does not have a cousin Leo.
(Man:)Au contraire.
(Man:)I'm 26 years old...
...I'm originally from "Denton, Texas,"
but I was a Navy brat.
(Man:)I was brought up on a variety
of military bases around the world.
(Man:)As a result, I've often felt like an outsider,
never really fitting in...
(Man:)...probably the reason
for my substance-abuse problem.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me, we just went over this.
As the middle child, your addiction
is rooted in your unmet need for attention.
Oh, Sheldon, are we really gonna go
with pop psychology?
(Sheldon:)For your information,
this is all based on solid research.
Just stick with the character profile
I wrote for you.
- Sheldon?
- I'm sorry.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, this is Toby Loobenfeld.
(Sheldon:)He's a research assistant
in the particle-physics lab...
...but he also minored in theater at MIT.
(Toby:)It was more of a double major, actually.
Theater and Physics.
(Toby:)You can guess which one
my bourgeois parents pushed me towards.
(Leonard:)Yeah, I got it.